all right today's C challenge the
scientist stealth no suppressors setting
UI and fast detection so you've got no
suppressors which means that will
literally going to have to knock every
single person out
instead and it also means that we're
going to have to find the second command
which might not be exactly the best
thing ever now aside from that we've got
hidden UI and FAS detection which is
like balancing
detection except that is far more
stressful now cyber if you could do me a
favor and not get caught over that that
would be
fantastic I mean that's convenient we
know who the second command is now so
so C I'm not going to go inside it's
fast detection right now all right and
that guard is going to detect me real
fast
so we're just going to wait here and
then we're going to have to realize that
is fast protection so we can't actually
lure anyone so hopefully you walk
towards us right now which is not
happening so we'll just make a cyber
problem we'll run past all of that and
we will hope that that guard does not
show up over here because if that
happens we're not going to be having a
good time
so we'll open up this door the guard
is did that guard go into the shed of
all places you know what let's not
question it we'll open up we'll take
this opportunity to open up this door we
will run as far away as
possible and the guards staying there
all right in that case hi there Falcon
nice to meet
you just don't be on radio all right I
mean we've got a screwdriver we'll
eventually need that so we might as well
grab that now all we got to do is make
our way back over there
and then afterwards not get attacked
this time which is far more stressful
than
it we'll just get this door open we'll
go inside and then afterwards cyber will
hopefully deal with the second command
and a decent amount of time
which that is not the second command hi
there I'm going to slide right past you
and then cyber is just a
guard which one is
it all right I'll grabb that key card
you don't get caught and then
afterwards actually I'm going to back
off to just so that cyber has an easier
time moving that back without getting
the tech bring it this way
don't why would you know what never mind
we'll take this risky time to go inside
which I mean it's not that bad but it
isn't great either hi that Guard we're
just going to walk right past you and
then afterwards we use the key card
reader and now all we got to do is wait
cyber you know you can come down here
right and help me deal with the
guard all right I suppose I'm doing this
myself then so in that case we'll wait
for this to complete which it should be
done soon hello
there and there we go that's that taken
care of and now all we got to do is use
that screwdriver we have to avoid these
guards actually first of all hi there
folks the control room doors on the
other side of course it is in that case
we'll go through here then
there are hi there there are a lot of
options over there and of course right
Falcons over there which means that we
can't actually do anything right now so
fcon if you can move right now that
would be
fantastic this is awkward there we go
and I watch as this gu turns my way and
then starts detecting me
which I'm actually very happy that it
there we go I mean at least it was timed
well so that shouldn't cause us too many
problems and then once Rivera gives the
information we can get this rewired
without getting caught because
everything went just fine after Falcon
left which it did not go just fine after
the Falcon left that guard is still
detecting me right now and I not feeling
comfortable about it all right we could
technically slide past both of these
guards and not get
seriously of course you know what our
priority should first of all not get
detected by Falcon but also not get
detected by any guardi in general so I
suppose of course we're going to go down
we're going to not get caught and then
we're just going to wait
here we're just going to you're still
there you are over here now walk past
right just move past me don't cause us
any problems and presumably there we go
now I can finally get the electrical
panel rewired and go inside
which surely this won't go horribly
wrong right
and that's everyone clear which this
door is precarious I should bag those
bodies up we will not do that though
because we can and then afterwards all
we got to do is manage taking people out
which how hard could that possibly be we
will start with Falcon and we will
remember that actually we should
probably bag up Falcon first just in
case anyone walks here and I'm realizing
that I actually don't have any solutions
for entering one of these there's a
guard over there I think I was being
hidden by that column or whatever that
is but we're just going to go in here
and take advantage of this time we have
and of course the W Cutters are here not
that we really need it but regardless
we're going to grab the USB mainly
because we can and now all we got to do
is clear the remaining Gods which can't
really happen if you're over here I mean
it's technically clear over there right
we could do this this is a bad idea so
we're just going to wait hold on it's
also like clear right now you know what
in that case let's try something
this is a very bad this is very bad
timing right
now that was not supposed to happen
we'll go down here I think cyber's going
to take that guard out and then
afterwards we're going to clear the
remaining guard Falcon ready out so that
means that we should be clearing the
entire map actually so we can do that
without any problems and all we got to
do is wait for Sparrow which hold on
let's do that and let's do that there we
go now Sparrow get us out of here before
cyber keeps that's just under 6 minutes
cheers everyone have a great time
[Music]